[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1973 movie Blackenstein used actual props from the 1931 film Frankenstein.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the morbid fear of thunderstorms?", "correct_answer": "Brontophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Triskadekaphobia", "Xylophobia", "Chionophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What breed is known as the favourite breed of Queen Elizabeth II?", "correct_answer": "Welsh Corgi", "incorrect_answers": ["Border Collie", "Old English Sheepdog", "Australian Cattle Dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Magnesium?", "correct_answer": "Mg", "incorrect_answers": ["M", "Mn", "Ma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This vegetable comes from the Andes in Peru and Bolivia, where people have known it for 2400 years. It became popular in Europe in 1780, when it first appeared in Ireland.", "correct_answer": "Potato", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabbage", "Beans", "Peas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This novella by H.P. Lovecraft was published in 1936 and is about a hybrid race of human/ fish/ frog people who inhabit a small town in Massachusetts.", "correct_answer": "The Shadow Over Innsmouth", "incorrect_answers": ["Something Wicked This Way Comes", "The Deep Ones", "The Gods of Pegana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are spotted hyenas considered an endangered species?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song from the movie Camp Rock was performed by Demi Lovato and Joe Jonas?", "correct_answer": "This Is Me", "incorrect_answers": ["Gotta Find you", "We Rock", "Who Will I Be"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what geological time period did the ammonites evolve?", "correct_answer": "The Devonian period", "incorrect_answers": ["The Silurian period", "The Triassic period", "The Carboniferous period"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where in the human body is the Golgi organ located?", "correct_answer": "In tendons", "incorrect_answers": ["Within the brain", "Within the cell", "In the eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did boxer Jack Johnson, Charlie Chaplin and actor, Errol Flynn all have in common?", "correct_answer": "They were all charged with the same crime", "incorrect_answers": ["They all died in Paris", "They died of the same causes", "They had the same birthday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The juice of what fruit is used for the preparation of the Cosmopolitan cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Cranberry", "incorrect_answers": ["Strawberry", "Peach", "Raspberry"]}]